Guide to the Reference Center for Marxist Studies Pamphlet Collection PE.043
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Jobs (17 pamphlets, brochures, and draft programs of the Communist Party, U.S.A.) (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - A Program for Jobs in N.Y. State. Council on Public Affairs N.Y. State American Labor Party, New York, NY. (2 copies), undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Burton, Bernard. Must We Have Depression? How to Keep Your Job. New Century Publishers, New York, NY., 1955 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Burton, Bernard. We Can Have Peace and Jobs! New Century Publishers, New York, NY., 1953 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Hudson, Roy. Post-War Jobs for Veterans Negroes Women. Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1944 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Preis, Art. Jobs for All. Pioneer Publishers, New York, NY., 1945 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Murray, Philip. C.I.O. Re-Employment Plan. C.I.O Department of Research and Education, Washington, D.C., undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Q. What's Happening to Our Jobs? Popular Economics Press, Somerville, MA., 1976 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Seniority, & Racism, The Fight for Jobs. Labor Education Fund, Chicago, IL. (2 copies), undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Sparks, Leonard. How to Win Jobs. Literature Distributors, New York, NY. (2 copies), undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - The American Way To Jobs, Peace, Democracy. New Century Publishers, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1954 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - The American Way to Jobs, Peace, Equal Rights and Democracy. New Century Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), 1954 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - The Income and Jobs Action Act. National Congress of Unemployed Organizations, Chicago, IL., undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - The Right to a Job. Daily World, New York, NY. (2 copies), undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - What's a Job?. Buffalo Labor Youth League, Buffalo, NY., undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Winternitz, J. The Problem of Full Employment: A Marxist Analysis in four lessons. Lawrence & Wishart., 1947 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Johnson, Oakley (2 pamphlets and reprints of articles) (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Oakley C. Campus Battles for Freedom in the Thirties. The Centennial Review. (2 copies), 1970 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Oakley C. My Grandson, Steve. New York, NY. (2 copies), 1970 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Oakley C. Preventive Remedial English in the Negro Secondary School. The Journal of Negro Education., 1949 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Oakley C. The Negro-Caucasian Club: A History. The American Students' First Inter-racial Organization., 1969 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Jones, Claudia (3 pamphlets and several articles by and about Claudia Jones) (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Jones, Claudia. An End to the Neglect of the Problems of the Negro Woman!. National Women's Commission, C.P.U.S.A., New York, NY., 1949 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Jones, Claudia. Life Every Voice - For Victory!. New Age Publishers, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1942 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Journalism (1 pamphlet) (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - What is the International Organisation of Journalists. The I.O.J. Fifth Congress in Budapest., undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Juvenile Delinquency (3 pamphlets) (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Neisser, Edith G. School Failures and Dropouts. Public Affairs Committee., 1963 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Weissman, Aaron. What's Behind "Juvenile Delinquency." New Century Publishers, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1955 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Kampuchea (12 pamphlets) (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - For Peace in Southeast Asia. International Forum on Peace in Southeast Asia, Phnom Penh, People's Republic of Kampuchea., 1983 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Gornicki, Wieslaw. Vietnam- Kampuchea 1979: An eye-witness Report. World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Kampuchea: A Blood Debt is Paid. Afro-Asian Publications., 1979 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Mosyakov, Dmitry. The Crimes of the Pol Pot Regime. Novosti Press Agency Publishing House, Moscow., 1984 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Recognise Now - People's Republic of Kampuchea. Information Centre of the World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland., 1980 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Samphan, Khieu. A Genuine Peace Will Be Restored in Cambodia After the Cessation of All Intervention of the U.S. Imperialists. The Royal Government of National Union of Kampuchea., 1975 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Shubin, Valentin. History Condemns Genocide Conducted Under Pol Pot. Novosti Press Agency Publishing House, Moscow., 1985 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Simonov, Vladimir. Kampuchea: Crimes of Maoists and Their Rout. Novosti Press Agency Publishing House, Moscow., 1979 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Some Evidence: Of the Plots Hatched by the Beijing Expansionists and Hegemonists Against the Kampuchean People. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, People's Republic of Kampuchea., 1982 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Thai Policy vis-a-vis Kampuchea. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, People's Republic of Kampuchea., 1983 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - The National United Front for the Salvation of Kampuchea. NUFSK Information Service., 1979 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Vats, Bhagat. The Kampuchea Holocaust and its Aftermath. World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland., undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Katayama, Sen (4 pamphlets) (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Yoneda, Karl G. The Heritage of Sen Katayama. Political Affairs Reprints, New York, NY. (4 copies), circa 1975 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Katovis, Steve (1 pamphlet) (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Magil, A.B. and Joseph North. Steve Katovis: Life and Death of a Worker. International Pamphlets, New York, NY., 1930 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Kent, Rockwell (1 pamphlet and articles about Rockwell Kent) (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Kent, Rockwell. What is an American? New Masses, Inc., 1936 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Kent, Sally. Rockwell Kent's Engagement with Life. American Dialogue., 1971 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Kentucky (1 pamphlet) (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Lessons of Louisville a White Community Response to Black Rebellion. Southern Conference Educational Fund, Louisville, KY., undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Kenya (1 pamphlet) (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Terror in Kenya: The Facts Behind the Present Crisis. W.F.T.U. Publications, Ltd., London., 1952 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Kerr, Charles H. and Co. (1 pamphlet) (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - The Story of a Socialist Publishing House. Charles H. Kerr and Company, Chicago, IL., undated (Box 59, Folder 10)
- King, Martin Luther, Jr. (7 pamphlets, brochures) (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Aptheker, Herbert. Dr. Martin Luther King, Vietnam and Civil Rights. New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1967 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Killens, John Oliver. Martin Luther King Memorial. Trident Press., 1967 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - King, Jr., Martin Luther. An Appeal to the Honorable John F. Kennedy President of the United States for National Rededication to the Principles of the Emancipation Proclamation and for an Executive Order Prohibiting Segregation in the United States of America. Southern Christian Leadership Conference, Atlanta, GA., 1962 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - King, Jr., Martin Luther. Letter from Birmingham City Jail., 1963 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - King, Jr., Martin Luther. Why We Can't Wait. Harper & Row, Publishers, New York, NY., 1963 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - King, Jr., Martin Luther. Workers Conferences- Organize Now! Southern Christian Leadership Foundation, Chicago, IL., undated (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Martin Luther King Jr.: Living the Dream. American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, Washington, D.C., 1985 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Shapiro-Bertolini, Ethel. "I Never Died, Said He.". Published by the author. (2 copies), 1970 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - These Questions Have Been Asked...does Martin Luther King, Jr. have the Right? the Qualifications? the Duty? to speak out on Peace. SCLC. (2 copies), undated (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Korea I (20 pamphlets) (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - American Armed Intervention in Korea. Soviet News, London., 1950 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Burchett, Wilfred. The Struggle For Korea's National Rights. Foreign Languages Publishing House, Pyongyang, Korea., 1974 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Facts on Korea and Washington Witch Hunt and the Far East. Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy, New York, NY., 1950 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Facts on the Korean Crisis. Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy, New York, NY. (3 copies), undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Hall, Gus. Hands Off Korea and Formosa. New Century Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), 1950 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Kim Il Sung. Korea Must be Reunified: A Call for Friendship Between the Peoples of the United Statess and the Democratic Peoples Republic of Korea. American-Korean Friendship and Information (AKFIC), New York, NY., undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Korea: Uneasy truce in the land of the morning calm. American-Korean Friendship and Information Center (AFKIC), New York, NY. (3 copies), undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Mann, Robert. From Korea Truce to World Peace. N.Y. State Communist Party, New York, NY., undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Operation War Shift. American-Korean Friendship and Information Center, New York, NY., 1971 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Press Conference Given in Pyongyang by Former South Korean Airmen Who Came Over to the Northern Half of the Republic. Pyongyang, D.P.R.K., 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Press Conference: Reporters from Many Countries of the World Meet Crewmen of the U.S. Imperialist Armed Spy Ship "Pueblo." Korean Central News Agency, Pyongyang, D.P.R.K., undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Pyongyang Declaration of the Journalists of the Whole World Fighting Against the Aggression of U.S. Imperialism. The International Conference on the Tasks of Journalists of the Whole World in Their Fight against the Aggression of U.S. Imperialism, Pyongyang, Korea., 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Story About Mad Dog (Letters from South Korea). Foreign Languages Publishing House, Pyongyang, Korea., 1977 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - The Communique on the Fifth Plenum of the Fourth Central Committee of the Korean Workers' Party. Foreign Languages Press, Peking., 1963 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Korea II (15 pamphlets, brochures) (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Fast, Howard. Korean Lullaby. American Peace Crusade, New York, NY. (2 copies), undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Jim Crow "Justice" in Korea: The Case of Lieutenant Leon Gilbert. Trade Union Youth Committee for the Freedom of Lieut. Gilbert, New York, NY. (2 copies), undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Korean Industry. Foreign Languages Publishing House, Pyongyang., 1959 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - The Land Law of the Democratic People's Republic of Korea. Foreign Languages Publishing House, Pyongyang, Korea., 1988 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - The Lodestar. Foreign Languages Publishing House, Pyongyang, Korea., 1986 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Our Party's Policy for the Building of an Independent National Economy. Foreign Languages Publishing House, Pyongyang, Korea., 1975 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Mann, Robert. From Korean Truce to World Peace. N.Y. State Communist Party, New York, NY. (2 copies), undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Meeting of Parties Which Will Cause a Split Must Be Averted. Foreign Languages Press, Peking., 1965 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Morris, Richard. What's Happening in Korea? New Century Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Strong, Anna Louise. In North Korea: First Eye-Witness Report. Soviet Russia Today, New York, NY., 1949 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - The Delegation. Women's International Democratic Federation., 1951 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - The U.S. Imperialists Bend Their Knees Again Before the Korean People. Foreign Languages Publishing House, Pyongyang, Korea. (2 copies), 1969 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Krupskaya (3 pamphlets) (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Bobrovskaya, C. Lenin and Krupskaya. Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), 1940 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Krushchov, N.S. (1 brochure) (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Address of N.S. Khrushchov. Council of Ministers of the USSR., 1959 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Ku Klux Klan (7 pamphlets) (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - De Silver, Albert. The Ku Klux Klan. American Civil Liberties Union, New York, NY., circa 1921 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Jameson, Jack. Night Riders in Sunny Florida. Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY., 1936 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Morris, George. The Black Legion Rides. Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY., 1936 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Russo, Pasquale. Ku Klux Klan Church and Labor. Published by the author, Chicago, IL., 1923 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Turner, John. The Ku Klux Klan a History of Racism and Violence. Southern Poverty Law Center, Montgomery, AL., 1982 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - We Won't Go Back! the Rise of the Ku Klux Klan and the Southern Struggle for Equality. Southern Equal Rights Congress, Mobile, AL., 1980 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    Folder contains 7 pamphlets.
- Labor (27 pamphlets) (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - A Policy for American Labor. New Century Publishers, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1958 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - American Labor Today. Political Affairs, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1960 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Come Out Swinging! Labor Education Fund, Chicago, IL. (2 copies), undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Dunn, Robert W. Company Unions Today. International Pamphlets, New York, NY., 1935 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Foster, William Z. Danger Ahead for Organized Labor. New Century Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), 1948 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Green, Gil. Guideline for Individual and Collective Study: What's Happening to Labor. International Publishers, New York, NY., undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Hall, Gus. Hard Hats and Hard Facts. New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1970 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Hall, Gus. Labor Unity: Why a Left-Center Coalition?, undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Hall, Gus. Why a Left-Center Coalition? Political Affairs, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1978 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Hall, Gus. Would You Believe...U.S. Workers Running the Economy? New Outlook Publishers & Distributors, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1980 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Hudson, Roy. Trends in the Labor Movement. Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1941 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Kelber, Harry. A Report To Working People., 1975 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - King, Judson. The T.V.A. Labor Relations Policy at Work. The National Popular Government League, Washington, D.C., 1940 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Labor Has Always Led. A UAW-CIO Publication, Detriot, MI., 1948 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Morris, George. District Council 9 Members Deserve a Better Deal. Publishers New Press, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1965 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Morris, George. Outlook for a New Labor Advance. The New Press Publishers, Inc., New York, NY. (2 copies), undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Morrison, Frank. Union and Non-Union Shop., undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Organized Labor- New Times, New Problems, New Ideas. Communist Party, USA, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1985 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Perlo, Victor. American Labor Today. New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), 1968 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Perlo, Victor. Labor conditions in the United States. World Marxist Review., undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Schendel, Herman. Why Work for Nothing? Chicago, IL. (2 copies), 1946 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Seidman, Joel. Introduction to Labor Problems. Brookwood Labor Publications, Katonah, NY. (2 copies), 1936 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Todes, Charlotte. The Injunction Menace. International Pamphlets, New York, NY., 1932 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Labor Looks at Europe. American Committee to Survey Labor Conditions in Europe, New York, NY., 1951 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Williamson, John. Two Conventions of Labor: The Situation in the Trade Union Movement. New Century Publishers, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1949 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Zugsmith, Leane. L is for Labor: A Glossary of Labor Terms. League of Women Shoppers, New York, NY., undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Labor: African Americans (13 pamphlets, bulletins) (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Black Americans: A Decade of Occupational Change. U.S. Department of Labor, Bureau of Labor Statistics, Washington, D.C., 1972 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Dudnick, Robert. Black Workers in Revolt. Radical Education Project, Detroit, MI. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Falcone, Nicholas S. The Negro Integrated. New York State War Council, Committee on Discrimination in Employment, New York., 1945 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - McKenzie, Alan and Henry Doliner. The Negro Worker in the ERB. Association of Workers in Public Relief Agencies of the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, New York, NY., 1937 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Organized Labor and the Black Worker. United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America (UE), New York, NY., 1967 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Proctor, Roscoe. Black Workers and the Class Struggle. New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY. (2 copies), 1972 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Robeson, Paul. Forge Negro-Labor Unity for Peace and Jobs. Political Affairs Reprints, New York, NY. (3 copies), 1976 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Seidenberg, Jacob. Negroes in the Work Group. New York State Council of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell University, Ithaca, NY., 1950 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Simon, Jean. Desegregation! Labor's Stake in the Fight for Negro Equality. Pioneer Publishers, New York, NY., 1955 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - The Economics of Prejudice. National Union of Marine Cooks & Stewards Research Department, San Francisco, CA., 1952 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - The Negro in 1944. National Political Action Committee, C.I.O., New York, NY., undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - The Negro in the Railroad Industry. Railroad Employees Association Against Discrimination, New York, NY., undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Working and Fighting Together Regardless of Race, Creed, Color or National Origin. CIO Committee to Abolish Racial Discrimination, Washington, D.C., 1943 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Folder contains 14 pamphlets.
- Labor: Archives (articles) (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Labor Archives Roundtable of the Society of American Archivists: A Directory and Concise Guide to Holdings. Wayne University Press. (3 copies), 1992 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Labor: Auto Workers (11 pamphlets) (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Building the Union. International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW-CIO), Detroit, MI., 1945 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Edelen, C.G. "Pop". Appeal to Reason. Unity Press., undated (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - How the Auto Workers Won. Daily Worker, New York, NY., undated (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Levinson, Edward. Rise of the Auto Workers. International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW-CIO), Detroit, MI., 1943 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Raushenbush, Carl. Fordism. League for Industrial Democracy, New York, NY., 1937 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - The "Productivity" Hoax! - and Auto Workers' Real Needs!. New Outlook Publishers, New York, NY. (3 copies), 1970 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - "To Unite...Regardless". International Education Department, UAW-CIO, Detroit, MI., undated (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Labor: Civil Rights and Liberties (1 pamphlet) (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Labor Injunctions. Committee on Labor Injunctions, New York, NY., 1931 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Labor: Collectors Exchange (contains materials published by the Collectors Exchange) (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Collector's Exchange. Vol. I, No. 2. Grand Rapids, MI., 1971 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Collector's Exchange. Vol. I, No. I. Grand Rapids, MI., 1971 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Collector's Exchange. Vol. I, No. 3. Grand Rapids, MI., 1971 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Collector's Exchange. Vol. I, No. 4. Grand Rapids, MI., 1972 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Collector's Exchange. Vol. I, No. 5. Grand Rapids, MI., 1972 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Collector's Exchange. Vol. I, No. 6. Grand Rapids, MI., 1972 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Collector's Exchange. Vol. II, No. 1. Grand Rapids, MI. (2 copies), 1972 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Collector's Exchange. No. 8. Grand Rapids, MI., 1975 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Collector's Exchange. No. 9. Grand Rapids, MI., 1975 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Labor: Company Unions and Management (6 pamphlets, reports, manuals, and a leaflet) (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Mass-Layoff Mergers in Communications. American Communications Association, CIO, New York, NY., undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - People vs. Rabbits. National Association of Manufacturers, New York, NY., undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Seidman, Joel. The Company Union. Brookwood Publications, Katonah, NY., 1936 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - The Stock Option Scandal. Industrial Union Department, AFL-CIO, Washington, D.C., undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Zimand, Savel. The Open Shop Drive Who is Behind it and Where Is it Going?. Bureau of Industrial Research, New York, NY., 1921 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Labor: CPUSA Positions (3 pamphlets) (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Foster, William Z. The Strike Situation and Organized Labor's Wage and Job Strategy. New Century Publishers, New York, NY., 1945 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Hall, Gus. Labor at the Turning Point: Labor Program of the Communist Party, USA. Communist Party, USA, Youngstown, OH. (2 copies), 1995 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Morris, George. Outlook for a New Labor Advance. The New Press Publishers, New York, NY., undated (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Swift, John. Some Problems of Work in Right-Led Unions. New Century Publishers, New York, NY., 1952 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Labor: Electrical Workers (12 pamphlets and a sample contract. Most pamphlets published by the United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE)) (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - A little bit of UE history You Should Know... United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America (UE), New York, NY., 1968 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - A Yankee Toolmaker Abroad. American Committee to Survey Labor Conditions in Europe., undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Biography of a Labor Union: A Chronicle of the International Bortherhood of Electrical Workers. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Washington, D.C., undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - For the general welfare. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, New York, NY., 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Maltes, James J. The Members Run this Union! An Answer to the Saturday Evening Post. United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America (UE-CIO), New York, NY., 1947 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Sample Contract. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, CIO, New York, NY., undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - The Facts Speak for Themselves! United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE), New York, NY., 1950 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - The Proud Record of an American Union! United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE), New York, NY., 1950 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - The UE Record: Our Gains of 11 Years and the Legislative Drive to Destroy Them. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE-CIO), New York, NY., 1947 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Thirst for Learning...a lifetime need. United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America (UE), New York, NY., 1973 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Wallace, Henry A. "Let's Come Out Fighting!" UE Convention, Boston, MA., 1947 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - What should union officials be paid? United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America (UE), New York, NY., undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Who Does the Work? United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE), New York, NY., 1951 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Your Union at Work. National Office, United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America, New York, NY., 1940 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Labor: Education (4 pamphlets) (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - 1926-1943 Yearbook of Workers' Education. American Labor Education Service, Inc., New York, NY. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Labor and Education: Our Greatest Resource, Don't Sell Them Short. Congress of Industrial Organizations, Washington, D.C., undated (Box 62, Folder 2)